let quiz   =[
    {question: "What is the absolute value of|-239|? ",
option:[
    0,
    239,
    -239,
    1,

],
answer:2, 
},

{
    question: "If 43m=0.086,then m has the value____ " ,
option:[
    0.002,
    0.02,
    2,
    0.2,


],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "Find the mean if the sum of 18 observations is 90.",
option:[
    4,
    5,
    6,
    9,


],
answer:2, 
},
{question: "Write an equation for if you take away 6 from 6 times Y you get 60.",
option:[
    "6Y-6=60",
    "6Y+6=60",
    "6Y*6=60",
    " None of these",

],
answer:1, 
},

{
    question: "What do we call an angle which exactly measures 90 degree?",
option:[
    "An obtuse angle",
    "An acute angle ",
    "A reflex angle",
    "A right angle",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Sum of three angles of a triangle is :",
option:[
    "170 degree",
    "90 degree",
    "180 degree",
    "360 degree ",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "An angle is of 50 degree then its congruent angle is of :",
option:[
    "40 degree",
    "45 degree",
    "60 degree",
    "50 degree",

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Convert 0.09 into percent." ,
option:[
    "9%",
    "8%",
    "8.5%",
    "7%",


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "The numerator of the rational number 1/100 is",
option:[
    100,
    1,
    10,
    99,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "How many perpendicular lines can be drawn to a line from a point not on it?",
option:[
    0,
    2,
    1,
    "infinite",

    
],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "The perimeter of a recangle is 30 m.Its length is 10 m. Its breadth is _____.",
option:[
    "5 m",
    "10 m",
    "15 m",
    "3 m",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "How many terms are there in the expression '1.2ab-2.4b+3.6a?'",
option:[
    2,
    3,
    4,
    1,

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "How many symmetry are there in an equilateral triangle ",
option:[
    3,
    2,
    1,
    0,

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "With respect to which of the following operations is closure property satisfied by the set of integers?",
option:[
    "+,x",
    "+,/,x",
    "+,x,-",    
    "+,-,/",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "The number of faces of a cube is ",
option:[
    8,
    6,
    12,
    3,

],
answer:2, 
}]